https://www.thinkdomains.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Domains and Business at ThinkDomains.com
Making A Difference in Small Business with Domain Names
HomeBlogConsultingContactDomain BlogsResourcesBusiness FinancingDomain BrokersHostingSocial MediaBusiness PlanningInfoAboutProject InquiryDomains For SaleAdvertise HomeBlogConsultingContactDomain BlogsResourcesBusiness FinancingDomain BrokersHostingSocial MediaBusiness PlanningInfoAboutProject InquiryDomains For SaleAdvertise
Domains and Business at ThinkDomains.com > Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.In Addition;Thank you for reviewing our policies regarding any personal information you may choose to provide at our website. We take your privacy very seriously and carefully protect any and all information entrusted to us. We only collect information that helps us serve you better and that you voluntarily provide. We do not share your information with anyone else unless you’ve approved of such sharing in advance.The following types of information may be collected at this website (if you volunteer it):your email addressyour first and last nameyour street address, city, state and ZIP Codepertinent information specific to an event or activity (where relevant)Third-Party Service ProvidersWe sometimes use other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders and delivering packages. They need access to some personal information in order to perform their duties but may not use this information for other purposes.More About Email & Postal AddressesIf you supply us with your email and/or postal addresses, and do not specify otherwise, you may receive periodic messages from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events.If, later, you decide you no longer wish to receive such messages, you may let us know by sending an e-mail, calling or writing us. To ensure we correctly identify you (many names are similar), please be sure to include your complete name and address and all email addresses that may be associated with your record. This helps us accurately locate your information in our file. Such information will only be used to comply with your request.ContactThink Domains Consulting @ Sales 303-484-1245 EmailRecent Posts How many domains to have for your business? Cart Before the Horse ? How not to pick a domain name for your startup Exact Match Domains Control EnterSocialBlogProject InquiryContactDomains For SaleAdvertiseRecommendPrivacy Policy Copyright ©
2020 ThinkDomains.com | WebVisionUSA.com. All rights reserved. This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary Always Enabled
